What are you looking at?
Look at those dark circles.
Where have you been fooling around?
I had a task.
My days and nights have been flipped
for a whole month.
I finally got a day off,
but you came back at the wrong time.
I came back at the wrong time?
Fine, I'll leave.
Get lost.
I'm getting lost then.
Let's go eat.
They renovated the place
and raised the prices.
How could I rip you off
if it wasn't expensive?
Is this okay, Captain Li?
Does this make up for it?
Is this really necessary?
Is it a celebration or a trap?
Celebration or trap,
when have I ever made you pay?
Just eat,
stop complaining.
Waiter, you can leave us for now.
We have things to discuss.
Okay, thank you.
Come on, Captain Li.
Long time no see.
I'm on a mission.
I can't drink.
Drink it yourself.
Are you in some kind of trouble?
Explain yourself before we eat.
Xingchen,
you have to help me.
Understood.
Meaning Song Yanfei
disappearing from your life
was a huge blow to you, right?
So
he's the one you hate the most.
It's more than that.
Later, I kept looking for him,
only to find out
he returned to Checheng.
I learned his family had an emergency.
What year and month?
October 22, 2002.
This is the day.
Xingchen,
you gotta help me.
What are you doing?
Get up, you hear me? Get up.
You have to help me.
Man, I haven't slept in days.
Besides, I'm glad you came.
You finally
came back,
and you just had to pull this stunt.
Really?
Get up. Get up and talk.
Get up.
You've been so tired lately.
You're on a mission, right?
Keeping the chairman of Dacheng Group
under residential surveillance,
right?
You shouldn't be asking this.
It's my job.
I can't tell you.
It's protocol.
Besides, it has nothing
to do with you, right?
It does, Li Xingchen.
It has everything to do with me.
It makes sense
that you don't know.
When we were kids,
my parents were always abroad.
Song Yucheng is your dad?
I have to go.
It's not appropriate
for us to meet right now.
I just have a few words to say.
My dad was framed.
You have to help me.
Yanfei,
you need to believe that the law is just.
Also, I might as well break protocol
and tell you something.
We're investigating it.
There's still hope.
It's best if we wait
for the final results,
okay?
I'm afraid he'll face retaliation.
I'm a cop.
While we monitor him,
we'll also protect his safety.
Li,
Song Yucheng has been in there
for over three hours
without moving.
When will the higher-ups give the order
to just take him away?
Should be soon.
You look like
you didn't get enough sleep.
I'm fine. What about you?
You stayed up all night yesterday, right?
If you're tired,
get some rest.
I'll keep an eye on him.
Okay. I'm fine.
Thanks for your hard work.
Xingchen, I'm going to the restroom.
Officer,
my stomach hurts so much.
I feel terrible.
S-Stomach hurts?
Yes.
Could you
pour me a cup of hot water?
Sir,
please wait a moment.
I'll pour it for you
when my colleague gets back,
okay?
Look at my age.
I'm really in pain.
Please,
just get me some hot water.
Xingchen,
make sure my dad
gets enough to eat.
Pour it over there?
Yes.
Wait a moment.
I-It won't open.
After his father passed away,
he stayed cooped up
at his grandparents' house,
refusing to go out
or contact anyone.
Later,
he went to Shanghai.
Two years ago,
his relatives
found him a job here.
When I saw him again,
it was already two years ago.
So from his
sudden disappearance
to your reunion,
seven years had passed.
Right.
Over six years.
Actually, I had already given up
looking for him back then.
I went back to Beijing
and continued working there.
Until that year,
the school where my mom worked
was entering a dance competition
and needed an instructor,
so she called me back to help.
During the rehearsal
at the Cultural Palace,
I saw him from behind.
Three curves.
One, two, three, four,
five, six, seven, eight.
Expressions.
Two, two, three, four,
five, six, seven, eight.
Three, two, three, four,
Four, two, three, four,
five, six, seven, eight.
Five, two, three, four,
Okay, strike a pose.
Okay.
Six, two, three, four,
five, six, seven, eight.
Mr. Jiang,
I need to step out for a moment.
Four, five, six, seven, eight.
Keep going.
Song Yanfei!
Yanfei,
Song Yanfei,
Song Yanfei, come out!
Hello,
Mr. Jiang.
Ms. Shen, it's time for class.
When are you coming back?
Okay, I'll be right back.
Shen Xi,
Where have you been all these years?
Why did you leave without saying a word?
Why did you leave me all alone?
I'm sorry.
I-I
missed you too.
Missed me?
Six years.
Six whole years.
I couldn't find you
no matter how hard I tried.
And you say you missed me?
Say something!
I'm sorry.
I don't want to hear 'I'm sorry.'
Tell me why.
What exactly happened?
I'll tell you everything.
Before that day,
I thought
I would never forgive
Song Yanfei in my life.
I thought the next time I saw him,
I would rush up
and slap him in the face.
But
when we actually met,
these thoughts in my head
couldn't control my body.
So you listened to his explanation.
He told you about his past, right?
Actually,
I recognized you on our blind date.
Song Yanfei mentioned you to me.
He said
his dad's incident implicated you too.
So you were transferred from the CID
to the traffic police. 045509.
Your name is so easy to remember. 09.
Li Xingchen,
it has a very artistic vibe.
the name is quite artsy.
It's a pity
we're not a good match.
I got rejected right
at the self-introduction.
Sorry.
I still have some unfinished business.
Until I figure that out,
it's hard for me
to start a new relationship.
Got it.
It's
about your ex,
right?
You got hurt.
So you can't get over it anytime soon?
No.
Did I say something wrong?
What?
Why are you writing down everything?
You don't need to write down my stuff.
Let's not talk about things
unrelated to the case.
And then?
You guys made up?
Not only did we make up,
but we also started
working on the dance drama together again.
Since then,
he worked in Checheng
while I drifted in Beijing.
But it's easier said than done.
We've met with countless investors
and sponsors.
Please trust me.
This dance drama will definitely
make you money, really.
Yes, please give us a chance.
We will definitely surprise you.
I'm really sorry.
We've discussed it,
and this drama is indeed great.
But it doesn't fit our market positioning.
We'll pass this time.
Which part doesn't fit
the market positioning?
We can talk about it.
Yes, we can make adjustments.
Just tell us what to change.
The decision is final.
Okay,
thank you.
Sorry, we're not interested.
If you have any thoughts, please tell us.
We can discuss it.
Yes, please take another look.
Right.
Thank you.
Our "Circle" is
a realistic
dance drama confronting
contemporary society.
It's really good.
Please take another look.
There are very few like it.
So it will definitely make money, really.
It's very meaningful.
We're not just a simple...
It's okay.
Let's go.
Please take another look.
We won't let you down.
Mr. Zhang,
please just take one more look.
The structure of our script
is really excellent.
Please. I'm not interested.
Mr. Zhang,
we will definitely make you money.
Really. Okay, okay.
Just give us a chance.
I'll think about it then.
We can communicate anytime.
Okay, okay.
We can really
revise it.
Okay, okay.
Thank you, Mr. Zhang.
Let us know if you have any questions.
Okay, okay.
Thank you.
Um,
Mr. Zhang, we'll keep in touch.
Okay, okay. Sure, sure.
Thank you, Mr. Zhang.
Thank you.
I think it should work out.
I hope we succeed.
At that time,
we were almost in despair.
We never knew
it would be so hard to raise
a few hundred thousand for production.
Until one day,
Song Yanfei saw a notice
for a competition.
You mean
the Peach Blossom Cup
sponsored by Wending Group,
right?
Yes.
Although it's a small competition
limited to our city,
Bureau-8240514
the prize money is substantial.
300,000 yuan
can cover most of the
dance drama's rehearsal costs.
As long as I get this money
and we pull in some more investment later,
it's basically a done deal.
So you completely left Beijing
for this competition?
After coming back,
I lived with my parents for a few days.
But I felt
it was really inconvenient
for dance practice,
so I thought about finding a place
to live alone.
At the time, I even discussed
living with Song Yanfei.
Soon,
we found this place
with a rooftop.
But who knew
Song Yanfei kept making excuses
about being busy with work.
I even had to move by myself.
Why did Song Yanfei become
the person I hate the most
when we met again?
Because of betrayal.
He chose Gao Yayan
for the dance drama.
The most ridiculous part is that
I was the one
who introduced Gao Yayan to him.
Starring
(in alphabetical order by surname)
Li Xingchen
F Xiaotong
Li Xingchen, Yu Xiaotong
Song Yanfei, Wang Zhiyong (Wang Ruizi)
Special Appearance
(in alphabetical order by surname)
Xiao Ze, Wang Hao
Special Appearance
Yan Yongmei, Fang Ming (Fang Xingyi)
Feng Shu, Liu Yakun
Jiang Dahai, Liu Zheting (Liu Zheting)
Bai Xiaosi, Liu Xiaolong (Liu Xu)
Bai Sha, Li Xintong
Mu Liyan, Chen Yongxia
Weng Wei, Huang Fei (Huang Jingxin)
Bai Jiuzhou, Qin Peng
Gao Yuhai, Cao Haitao (Cao Jingshi)
Weng Wei, Huang Fei (Huang Jingxin)
Cast (in alphabetical order by surname)
Forensic Doctor Cheng
Forensic Doctor Chenggong
Li Xingchen's Classmate, Liu Haohan
Young Li Xingchen, Li Yuanche
Young Song Yanfei, Chen Nuoyan
Investor, Zha Minxin
Lead Singer, Xu Weina
Li Xingchen's Classmate, Gao Jingman
Xiao Ze's Father, He Meng
Mother, Zhao Yue'en
Xiao Ze's Mother, Zhao Yue'en
Xiao Ze's Relatives, Li Ming, Wang Zhilei
Assistant, Bai Zhihao
Wang Siyu
Zhao Wenjuan, Li Ziying
Female Classmate Yue Yue
Yao Sha
Li Xingchen's Classmate
Tang Tang, Dai Guoming
Yao Sha
Woman Sun Meili
Nanny Wang Chunyang
Shareholders Huang Xinyang, Wang Wentao
Girl Ying
Gao Yuhai's Secretary Du Du
Feng Shu's Secretary Dai Dai
Fleeing Driver Liu Haohan
Driver
Driver Wang Yiguo
Speaking Police Officer Wang Zhiguo
Waiter Liu Jiaqi
Auntie Tu Manxia, Huang Xinyang
Mother Liu Li
Middle-aged Man Wang Xinda
Driver Old Zhao Wei Hong
Qin Zhiqiang
Locksmith Fu Wang
Xiao Ze's Mother Pei Xiao
Stagehand Xiao Zhang
Police Colleague
Young Man Tang Yuye
Police Colleague Li Lijun
Receptionist Teacher Ren Jiefei
Female Secretary Qian Duoduo
Boss X Liu Junjie
Boss Liu Junjie
Driver Hu Huazheng
Scrap Yard Boss Zhang Li Chenghu
Wounded Person Xu Ganggang
Female Teacher Ai Li
Company Head Bai Yongjun
Yan's Mother Zhang Minghui
Woman Liu Yutong
Male Nurse Wu Zeyu
Female Nurse Bai Wanting
BBQ Restaurant Guests
Cheng Gong, Qiu Yaqiong
Female Nurse Bai Wanting
BBQ Restaurant Guests
Cheng Gong, Qiu Yaqiong
Guo Xinye
Speaking Man in Black: Zhu Yiqi
Bai Xiaosi's Stunt Double: Zhao Peng
Li Xingchen's Stunt Double: Tang Li
Taxi Driver
Song Yucheng: Liang Zhengchao
Cashier: Wu Tiantian
Yan Yongmei: Li Tianjun
Female Police Officer: Wu Lihua
Forensic Doctor Zhou Wen: Pei Xiao
Actor: Hu Zexuan
Execution Doctor: Geng
Cleaner Liu
Wang Yanmin
Streamer: Sun Jialiang
Extras: Da Qing, Liu Haohan
Receptionist: Wang Yanmin
Hot Pot Restaurant Owner: Qin Haitao
Receptionist Xiao Yu: Ren Jiefei
Crew
Chief Presenter: Xu Yue
Co-Presenters: Feng Fei, Guo Zhiyuan
Guo Guo
Chief Planner: Li Meina
Chief Distributor: Hu Kaichen
Police Consultant / Original Story: Fu Jun
Production Team
Chief Producers: Sui Dalong, Gao Jingman
Executive Producers: Peng Xia, Kang Hairu
Planner: Zhao Feng
Script Planner: Zhang Wanlu
Production Manager: Liu Zhilong
Unit Manager: Yin Zhongheng
Set Operations Team
Key Grip: Liu Yiqing
Yang Qunbao
Kitchen
Kitchen Manager: Yin Xiumei
Vegetable Washer: Hu Xiuxia
Li Zhiwei, Ma Yuan
Transportation Team
Wang Ji, Zhang Xiong
Li Xiaoche
Song Shuwei
Niu Yuwang, Wang Yiguo
Xiao Yucai, Liu Xin
Directing Team
Screenwriter: Yue Shunming
Director: Yue Shunming
Executive Director: Sui Chenggong
Script Supervisor: Li
On-Set Assistant Director: Liu Haohan
Casting Coordinator: Kang Hairu
Editing Team
Editor: Wu Yingjie
DIT: Jin Linxin
Sound Team
Production Sound Equipment Provided by
Beijing Wenhui Qiming Culture Communication Co., Ltd.
Sound Assistants: Wu Yingxue, Zhang Qichun
Art & Props Team
Production Designer: Zhao Daqian
Co-Production Designer: Gong Xueyuan
Wang Liqi
Assistant Art Director: Wang Tianyi
Action Props
Props Master: Sun Donghua
On-Set Assistant Supervisor: Li Yao
On-Set Supervisor: Hou Yonghao
Set Dressers: Zhang Li, Zhang Qingzhong
On-Set Assistant Supervisor: Li Yao
Camera Team
Director of Photography: Li Yixu
A Camera Operator: He Yong
A Camera Focus Puller: Yao Yonglei
A Camera Assistant: Li Xinghan
B Camera Operator: Zhao Shidian
B Camera Focus Puller: Li Chenlong
B Camera Assistant: Cao Xing
C Camera Operator: Ma Mingguo
B Camera Assistant
Camera Trainees: Guo Ruicai, Liu Shihao
Lighting Team
Gaffer: Gao Yun
Lighting Assistants:
Zhang Xiaoguang, Chang Lin
Terigun
Styling Team
Hair & Makeup: Yuan Zihan, Wang Peng
Wardrobe & Makeup Supervisor: Ma Yi
On-Set Hair & Makeup: Liu Lu, Guo Xinye
On-Set Wardrobe Supervisors:
Zhang Lei, Yi Junli
Marketing & Distribution Team
Marketing Director
Beijing This Is Cola Culture
Media Co., Ltd.
Li Yiyi
Marketing Director: Li Yiyi
Planning Director: Yang Liuting
Media Manager: Yue Yue
Project Coordinator:
Copywriters: Zhang Weirui, Li Ziwei
Video Editors: Wang Jiahui, Miao Wenbo
Ren Zhongjun
Graphic Design
Post-Production
Beijing Wenhui Qiming Culture
Communication Co., Ltd.
Post-Production Coordinator: Zhang Xiaoman
Post-Production Supervisor: Wu Wenhui
Colorist: Niu Xuerui
Post-Production Coordinator: Zhang Xiaoman
End Credits: Jin Linxin
Opening Titles: Gao Dong
Re-Recording Mixer: Zhang Kai
Subtitles: Su Li
Ambience Editor: Zhang Xinyu
Dialogue Editor
Sound Effects Editor: Zhang Xiaoman
Visual Effects
VFX Supervisor: Gao Dong
Beijing Wenhui Qiming Culture
Communication Co., Ltd.
VFX Artist: Jin Linxin
VFX Supervisor: Gao Dong
Compositor
Shang Chenyao
Music Production
Hong Kong, China Musical Theatre
Music Director: Xiao Zhuang
Score Production: Xiao Zhuang, Wang Daifu
Music Coordinators: Jiang Zheng,
Liu Zining
Score Production: Xiao Zhuang, Wang Daifu
Guitar: Liu Zining
Score Mixing: Zhao Yi
Vocal Recording: Zheng Suyang
Song Recording Studio:
Beijing Landuo Recording Studio
Song
"Brothers"
Performed by Yue Shunming
Arranged by Zhao Yi
Produced by Xiao Zhuang
Performed by Zhang Keying
"Song of Spring"
Yu Xiaotong
Lyrics by Yue Shunming
Children's Vocals: Zhang Maolin
Composed by Xiao Zhuang
Arranged by Xiao Zhuang
Produced by Xiao
"Promise"
Lyrics by Bai Yuxiang
Composed by Xiao
Arranged by Xiao Zhuang
Performed by Ben Damiao
Composed by Xu Yue
Performed by Xu Yue
"That's All"
Lyrics by Gao Jingman
Arranged by Wang Anyu
Performed by Xu
"Half a Beat Slower"
Performed by Xu Yue
Lyrics by Fan Fan
Composed by Xu Yue
Produced by Xu Yue
Performed by Wang Weijia
Lyrics by Bai
Composed by Xiao Zhuang
Arranged by Zhao Yi
"Only You" (Russian)
Performed by Liu Ruixun
Arranged by Zhao Yi
Produced by Xiao Zhuang
Publicity Department
of Shiyan Municipal Party Committee
Shiyan Public Security Bureau
Hubei Zhiyuxuan Agricultural
Technology Co., Ltd.
Shiyan Public Security Bureau
Hubei Zhiyuxuan Agricultural
Technology Co., Ltd.
Hubei Jiutouniao Catering
Management Co., Ltd.
Shiyan Dongfeng Hometown
Historical Materials Exhibition Hall
Shiyan Xiaowujia Catering
Management Service Co., Ltd.
Shiyan Dongfeng Hometown
Historical Materials Exhibition Hall
Dongfang Yuanzhi School,
Maojian District, Shiyan
Shiyan Hengjiu Kanghua Real Estate
Co., Ltd. (Longcheng Mansion)
Zesheng Property Services
Shiyan Hengjiu Kanghua Real Estate
Co., Ltd. (Longcheng Mansion)
Shiyan Mingxin Huizhi Dance Academy
Sunshine Dance Art Training School,
Maojian District, Shiyan
Meiyijia Convenience Store, No. 88
Gongyuan Road, Zhangwan District, Shiyan
Exclusive Social Media Platform
Chief Partner Media
Co-produced by
Sichuan Jiaodian Pictures
Co., Ltd.
Co-presented by
Sichuan Prism Creation Film
and Television Culture Co., Ltd.
Shanxi Chengyi Film
and Television Media Co., Ltd.
Sichuan Prism Creation Film
and Television Culture Co., Ltd.
Qinghe (Beijing) Culture Media
Co., Ltd.